http://www.opactive.com/content/privacy-policy

Testimonials
We Support !
(206) 304.5811info@opactive.com
Cart (0)
Testimonials
We Support !
Testimonials
We Support !
1Information Collection
Opportunity Interactive, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on www.opactive.com. Opportunity Interactive, Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.
2Registration
In order to use some areas of this Web site, a user must complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest.
3Order Fulfillment
We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used strictly for billing purposes and to fill customer orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.
4Newsletter Sign-up
We request an email address for the user to receive our newsletter, and it is used solely for that purpose. Signing up for our newsletter is voluntary.
5Log Files
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service. We use a tracking utility called Webtrends that uses log files to analyze user movement. [See the Profile section below.]
Communications from the Site
1Newsletter
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users' privacy we provide a way to unsubscribe at the bottom of each newsletter.
2Customer Service
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users' wishes.
3Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
4Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.
5Third Party Intermediaries
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
6Service Providers
We partner with Business Development Resources, Inc. to provide specific services. For example, business consulting, training, and software support services. When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, and other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
7Service Providers
We partner with Business Development Resources, Inc. to provide specific services. For example, business consulting, training, and software support services. When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, and other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
8Business Transitions
In the event Opportunity Interactive, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, user’s personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.
9Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Opportunity Interactive, Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. Links directly to the www.opactive.com website or any of its subdomains are not allowed without written permission from Opportunity Interactive. The only exception are links to the www.opactive.com home page used in conjuction with a marketing or link exchange program.
10Surveys
From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users’personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users’personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
11Third Party Intermediaries
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
12Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Opportunity Interactive, Inc. cannot be responsible for use of personal user information collected in chat rooms, message boards, and public forums.
13Third Party Intermediaries
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
14Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’. To learn more about SSL, follow this link http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/S/SSL.html . While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’information is protected. If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to info@opactive.com .
15Supplementation of Information
In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.
16Credit Check
For example, to determine if users qualify for financing, we use their name and social security number to request a credit report. Once we determine a user’s credit-worthiness, this document is destroyed.
17Purchasing History
In order for this Web site to enhance its ability to tailor the site to a user’s preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our partner, Business Development Resources, Inc., to create a personalized user profile. When a user makes a purchase from either of these two companies, the users' personal and demographic information is shared between the two companies.
18Enhancement of Marketing Profile
We purchase third party marketing data and add it to our existing user database to better target our advertising and provide pertinent offers we think our users would be interested in. We use this information to enhance or overlay the ‘profile’ of individual users. This aggregate marketing data is therefore tied to the users’ personally identifiable information. See also the "Profile."
19Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by emailing Customer Service . [Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed on the contact page of our web site].
20Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email and by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.
21Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact Customer Service or see the contact page of our web site.
Quick LinksHome
Opportunity Manager™
HVAC Showroom
Mobile Office
Recruit4Business
Company Info
Testimonials
Privacy Policy
Contact usOffice: Opportunity Interactive, Inc.19604 International Blvd., Ste. 101SeaTac, Wa 98188Phone: (206) 304.5811Fax: (206) 870.1820Toll Free: 1.877.816.6649E-Mail: info@opactive.com
Say Hello
Full Name *
Email Address *
Contact Number *
Message *
Copyright © 2000-2020, Opportunity Interactive, Inc., All Rights Reserved.
Call for more information: 1-877-816-6649
